[
    {
        "question": "Qual o valor da multiplicação: 3x7?",
        "choice1": "10",
        "choice2": "19",
        "choice3": "21",
        "choice4": "23",
        "choice5": "Nenhuma Das Alternativas",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Qual o valor da multiplicação: 7x5?",
        "choice1": "27",
        "choice2": "25",
        "choice3": "37",
        "choice4": "35",
        "choice5": "Nenhuma Das Alternativas",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "Qual o valor da multiplicação: 9x6?",
        "choice1": "56",
        "choice2": "54",
        "choice3": "60",
        "choice4": "64",
        "choice5": "Nenhuma Das Alternativas",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Quanto é 2x13?",
        "choice1": "26",
        "choice2": "23",
        "choice3": "24",
        "choice4": "36",
        "choice5": "Nenhuma Das Alternativas",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Quanto é 7x11?",
        "choice1": "70",
        "choice2": "73",
        "choice3": "77",
        "choice4": "76",
        "choice5": "Nenhuma Das Alternativas",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Quanto é 13x5?",
        "choice1": "60",
        "choice2": "55",
        "choice3": "50",
        "choice4": "70",
        "choice5": "Nenhuma Das Alternativas",
        "answer": 5
    },
    {
        "question": "Quanto vale 12x12?",
        "choice1": "124",
        "choice2": "134",
        "choice3": "144",
        "choice4": "154",
        "choice5": "Nenhuma Das Alternativas",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Quanto vale 7x8?",
        "choice1": "66",
        "choice2": "54",
        "choice3": "56",
        "choice4": "34",
        "choice5": "Nenhuma Das Alternativas",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Quanto vale 17x3?",
        "choice1": "31",
        "choice2": "43",
        "choice3": "57",
        "choice4": "51",
        "choice5": "Nenhuma Das Alternativas",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "Qual o valor da multiplicação: 7x7x3?",
        "choice1": "143",
        "choice2": "157",
        "choice3": "149",
        "choice4": "159",
        "choice5": "Nenhuma Das Alternativas",
        "answer": 5
    }
]